最后一单啦 姐妹
Last check, girl.
然后我男朋友鲍比就要到啦
And my boyfriend Bobby will be here soon.
他今晚又要来过夜
He's sleeping over again.
我男朋友 那个鲍比
My boyfriend, Bobby, I mean.
你知道那个帅哥鲍比 也就是我男朋友吧
You know that cute guy Bobby, my boyfriend?
我当然知道你男朋友鲍比啦
Oh, I know your boyfriend Bobby.
你提他的频率 就像奥普拉提自己好闺蜜一样
You name-drop him like you're Gayle and he's Oprah.
为什么你从来都不去鲍比家过夜啊
Why don't you ever stay at Bobby's?
他家再差也不能烂过我们家
His place can't be worse than ours.
除非他住在我们家墙里
Unless he's what's living in our wall.
不会的 在墙里哭的绝对是个女人
No, that's definitely a woman sobbing in there.
而且我不能去鲍比家过夜
And I can't stay at Bobby's
是因为他跟家人住在一起
'cause he lives at home with his family.
我都不知道他还跟家人同住呢
I didn't know Bobby lived at home.
真希望我还能搬回我家
Wish I could move back home.
可当年住的庞蒂克车已经停产了
They don't make Pontiacs anymore.
名闻遐迩的鲍比还跟家人住吗
The famous Bobby lives at home?
感觉你这次钓到"金龟婿"了呢
Sounds like you landed a real winner.
阿憨 其实鲍比会搬回家
Actually, Han, Bobby only moved back home
是因为他父亲去年过世了
because his dad died last year.
妈了个蛋
H-E-double hockey sticks!
我这辈子唯一一次吐槽别人
The one guy I take a shot at, ever,
这家伙居然是孤女安妮
and he's the freakin' Orphan Annie!
你好 我是鲍比
Hey, I'm Bobby.
我来找我女朋友卡洛琳
I'm looking for my girlfriend Caroline.
就是那个萌妹 卡洛琳
You know that cute girl, Caroline?
我女朋友
My girlfriend.
你叫鲍比 我是在哪听过你名字呢
Bobby. Now, where have I heard that name before?
鲍比 我男朋友 别闹了
Bobby, my boyfriend, stop.
趁我还没忘
Hey, before I forget.
我妈明天要举办一个派对
My mom is throwing a party tomorrow--
你疯啦
Are you crazy?
鲍比 永远不准在餐厅提起派对
Bobby, never discuss a party in the diner.
跟我们一起工作的这帮人
If the people we work with,
超超级给脸他们才勉强能称得上"人"
and I'm using "people" in the loosest sense possible--
如果这帮东西听到有派对 绝对会不请自来
if they hear about a party, they'll come to it!
我俩学了某印第安部落语
We had to learn Navajo
只为了能讨论周末要干嘛
just so we could talk about our weekend plans
而不用担心他们会听到
without them overhearing.
然后他们也学了那语言
And then they learned Navajo.
难怪昨天厄尔跟我要印第安贝壳串币
Now it makes sense that Earl asked me for wampum yesterday.
我妈明天要在我们家举办派对
Okay, so my mom is throwing this party at our house tomorrow.
你想来见见我家人吗
You want to meet my family?
我非常乐意跟他们见面
I'd love to meet them!
尤其是你母亲
Especially your mom.
不用说都知道 她绝对会爱死我
It goes without saying, but she's gonna love me.
为啥 她喜欢说话时会喷口水的人吗
Why? Does she love people who spit a little when they talk?
我说话才没有喷口水
I don't spit when I talk.
还真有 这次我看到唾沫星子了
Nope, I saw it that time.
不过没关系啦
But that's okay.
妈妈辈的人爱我的程度
Moms love me almost as much
跟卡车司机爱麦克斯有得一拼
as truckers love Max.
当一次挡泥板女郎 你就是司机一辈子女神
You model for one mud flap, you're made for life.
你也会一起来对吧 麦克斯
You're coming too, right, Max?
我全家人都会在
My whole family's gonna be there.
卡洛琳的全家人也都应该在场
Caroline's whole family should be there, too.
你这话真感人
Aww, that's so sweet.
听起来不错
Sounds good.
所以我大概几点带着献祭用浣熊入场
What time should I bring the sacrificial raccoon?
所以不是生日派对吗
Oh, is it not a birthday?
你能从那后面听到我们在聊什么吗
You could hear from back there?
几道墙外的我办公室也能听到
And through the wall in my office.
等不及去派对啦
Can't wait for the party.
我能带自制的果冻甜点吗
Can I bring a Jell-O dessert?
我有个新的皮卡丘模具我超想用看看
I have a new Pikachu mold I've been dying to try out.
是把你做出来的同个皮卡丘模具吗
Is it the same Pikachu mold that you came out of?
所以我们全都被邀请去的这派对
Ah, so, about this party we're all invited to,
是酒水无限畅饮
is it open bar,
还是我们又得自己去扫荡酒柜
or do we have to go through the cabinets again?
所以你妈都喷哪种香水
So what kind of perfume does your mom wear?
我得先知道 这样才能说我一直超爱那款
I need to know for when I tell her I've always loved it
真没想到我们喷同一款
and can't believe she wears it too.
我不知道 但如果你这辈子
I don't know, but please don't wear it
还想跟我滚床单 就请别喷那款
if you ever want to have sex with me again.
还有一件事
Oh, uh, one more thing.
千万别告诉她我在这过夜了
Don't tell her that I spent the night here.
她以为我是在我朋友布莱恩家睡
She thinks I stayed at my friend Brian's.
她这人比较传统一点
She's kind of old-fashioned.
也没你想象中那么传统
Can't be that old-fashioned.
她对你跟男性朋友布莱恩同睡都没意见了
She's cool with you sleeping with your friend Brian.
好啦 晚点见
All right, I'll see you later.
我得去帮忙我妈布置一下派对
I got to go help my mom set up for the party.
如果我给你的感觉像是坏男人
Uh, if I'm coming off as too much of a bad boy,
我可以收敛一点
I can tone it down.
我会记得在你家时亲脸颊的
I'll be sure to do cheek kisses at your house.
所以呢
So!
这派对会有大麻提供吗
Is there gonna be weed at this party,
还是我可以在那里卖大麻挣钱
or can I make some money selling?
麦克斯 让鲍比的母亲喜欢我真的很重要
Max, it is really important to me that Bobby's mom likes me,
所以我把你大麻藏了起来
which is why I hid your weed
然后买了个好礼物带去送她
and bought her a lovely gift to bring.
我一直都是穿低胸衣服来代替送礼物
In lieu of gifts, I always just wear a low-cut shirt.
但我看得出你为什么得买一份礼物
But I see why you had to buy something.
看 马卡龙
Look. Macaron.
你马卡"聋"了吧
Uh, you're maca-wrong,
因为那些已经是马卡隆[蛋白杏仁饼]了
'cause those are macaroons.
因为在我把它们的
And I think I maca-ruined them
馅都吃掉时 就买马卡毁了它们
when I ate the filling out of 'em.
等等 你要穿成那德行去鲍比母亲的派对吗
Wait, you're going to Bobby's mom's party dressed like that?
那你清楚你老公穿着清凉到像要去划船旅吗
Are you aware your husband is dressed for a canoe trip?
我用谷歌地球查过他家
I Google Earth-ed the house.
他家隔壁邻居家里有泳池
There's a pool at the house next door.
而且围墙很低
And a short fence.
其实派对取消了
Actually, the party was canceled.
我也很遗憾
I'm so sorry.
你们可能要到下辈子才能够见鲍比的家人了
You'll have to meet Bobby's family sometime never on.
是的 派对取消了
Yep, party canceled.
他家出现了个大沉洞
There was a sinkhole.
整个房子陷进去都找不到了
Uh, still haven't found the house.
所有人死光了
Everyone's dead.
这也太惨了吧
That's horrible.
我都预付了保姆薪水呢
I pre-paid a sitter.
那我们就在你们家玩吧
Oh, I guess we'll just hang out here then.
既然这里没有泳池游泳...
And since there's no pool--
好了好了 我服了你
Ahh! Okay! Okay, fine!
派对没有取消 也没有沉洞
The party's not canceled. There's no sinkhole.
没人死 四点来吧
No one's dead. Come at 4:00.
只求你们别丢我的脸
Just please don't embarrass me.
麦克斯 她那句话好像是对你说
Uh, I think that was directed at you, Max.
尴尬啦
Awkward.
我们提早到啦 因为妈妈辈的都喜欢人准时
We're here early, 'cause moms love promptness,
而且我们的优步司机正好在被警察追
and our Uber driver was on the front end of a police chase.
那你妥当了 我妈最爱的真人秀就是《执法先锋》
You're gonna nail it. My mom's favorite show's "Cops."
我是那节目的常驻犯人
Oh, I'm a series regular.
这楼梯不错啊
Oh, nice staircase.
你跟楼上的住客处得好吗
You get along with the folks that live up there?
看情况
Uh, sometimes.
看我姐姐们的心情吧
Depends how my sisters are feeling,
因为楼上也是我家的
'cause that is still part of the house.
你没跟我们说你住在城堡里啊
You didn't tell us you lived in a castle.
看看这电视还有椅子
Look at the TV and chairs!
这家具状况绝对是
You guys must've gotten this stuff
人家刚丢在前院你们就捡回家了的
right after they laid it out on the curb.
鲍比 我找到你六年级时话剧的节目单
Bobby, I found the program from your sixth grade play.
你当年表演得太棒了
You were so good.
跟莱昂纳多·迪卡普里奥差不多
Like Leonardo DiCaprio.
不过你没发福
Only not bloated.
妈 我演了一棵树 而且这样都被人嘘了
Ma, I played a tree, and I still got booed.
抱歉 她就喜欢吹嘘我
Sorry, she likes to brag about me.
这位是我母亲
This is my mom.
鲍比妈妈你好 我叫麦克斯
Hi, Bobby's mom. I'm Max.
请容我夸一下您这美轮美奂的房子
May I say you have a beautiful house?
这可是高度赞扬 因为我住过五间房子
And that's high praise, 'cause I've been in five.
我是卡洛琳
And I'm Caroline.
您身上的香味是我这辈子最爱的香味
Oh, that scent you're wearing is my all-time favorite.
我坐到一颗黄芥末蛋上了
I sat on a deviled egg.
希望您喜欢吃马卡龙
I hope you like macaron.
你觉得我还吃得不够吗
You don't think I have enough food?
这话可能听起来像神经病
I know this sounds insane,
但我不确定她有没有宇宙无敌第一爱我呢
but I don't know if she love-love-loved me.
别担心 她这个人有点慢热
Don't worry--she takes a little time to warm up,
等她热起来了
but when she does,
你也只会发现有一点点小差异
you'll only notice a little difference.
鲍比 我有个问题
Uh, Bobby--question.
你是怎么让英国女皇卖给你她的王座的啊
How did you get Queen Elizabeth to sell you her throne?
鲍比 你只邀请了女生吗
Bobby, you only invited girls?
你明知道我喜欢狼多女少的派对
You knew I wanted a sausage-fest.
我带了马卡龙来呢
I did bring macaron.
你一定是鲍比的姐姐丹妮斯吧
You must be Bobby's sister, Denise.
我叫卡洛琳
I'm Caroline.
我是麦克斯 我应该穿着尿布来的
I'm Max, and I should have worn a diaper here.
我说真的 鲍比 如果你都不邀请男生来
Seriously, Bobby, if you never invite any guys over,
我去哪泡到男人啊
how am I gonna find one?
妈把我相亲网站账号取消了
Ma cancelled my Match.Com account.
我才不要帮你付一个月9块99
I'm not paying $9.99 a month
好让你上网当个婊子
for you to be a slut!
妈 少管我闲事
Ma! Stay out of my business!
你总把我当30多岁那会儿对待
You treat me like I'm still in my 30s!
如果没有男人会来
Well, if there aren't gonna be any guys here,
那我要去呼个麻 拼拼图去了
I'm gonna go smoke a J and do my jigsaw.
等会绝对会去丹妮斯房里坐坐
Definitely popping by Denise's room later.
鲍比 我也不知道为什么
Bobby, I can't explain it,
但是你把汽水冰到车库里的冰箱后
but somehow, when you stock the Tab in the garage fridge,
味道喝起来就是赞
it just tastes better.
车库冰箱
Garage fridge?
你们是有多富啊
How rich are you people?
你知道谁会想喝冰汽水吗
You know who loved an ice-cold Tab?
杰西卡
Jessica.
妈 你不是吧
Ma! Really?
我特别交代过你别提起杰西卡
I specifically asked you not to bring up Jessica.
谁是杰西卡啊
Who's Jessica?
她是我前任
She's my ex.
我们一年前就停止交往了
We stopped dating over a year ago.
什么交往
Dating?
你们当年可是订了要订婚
You were engaged to be engaged!
我坐着 却犹如躺着
I'm sitting, but I'm lying down.
她是我唯一觉得
She was the only girl I ever thought
配得上我鲍比的女生
was good enough for my Bobby.
无意冒犯 亲 但你看她
No offense, hon, but look at her.
那个脸蛋 她完全有可能当一名牙科保健员
With that face, she could've been a dental hygienist.
她能荣登你家墙壁吗
She's on your wall?
单纯是为了要挡住丹妮斯
Only to cover a hole that Denise punched in it...
在我跟杰西卡分手时捶的洞
when I broke up with Jessica.
有人提起了杰西卡吗
Did someone say Jessica?
那是谁
Who is that?
拜托别说是杰西卡
And please don't say Jessica.
是我另一个姐姐克丽斯
That--that's my other sister, Chrissy.
她现在不太出她房门
She doesn't come out of her room these days.
-她还在哀悼期 -哀悼你父亲吗
- She's still in mourning. - Oh, over your dad?
是杰西卡
Over Jessica.
打从他俩分手后 她就不怎么出房间了
She hasn't come out of her room since they broke up.
她当时差点就要升职冻酸奶店副经理了呢
And she was this close to assistant manager at TCBY.
我已忘了杰西卡 但我家人还没
I'm over Jessica. My family less so.
我的老天爷
Oh, my God!
这椅子居然还有另一张给脚坐的椅子
This chair has another chair just for your feet!
鲍比 你为什么没告诉我杰西卡的事
Bobby, why didn't you tell me about Jessica?
我都跟你说过我爸坐牢的事了
I told you about my father being in prison.
没 你没说过啊
No, you didn't.
我老爸在坐牢
My father's in prison.
杰西卡对我无足轻重
Jessica's not important to me.
我基本就不会想到他 她就像美国在线即时通
I think about her so little, she might as well be AOL.
我还在用呢
I'm on AOL.
天啊 我们对彼此简直一无所知
Oh, my God, we know nothing about each other.
鲍比 厨房冰箱也是你在负责采买的吗
Bobby, did you stock the kitchen fridge, too?
里面的瓶装饮料 居然有玻璃瓶装
'Cause I'm getting that crisp, clean, bottle taste
那种干净清澈口感
from a can here.
我脱了鞋 希望你们不介意
I took my shoes off. Hope that's okay.
鲍比 别站在那里盯着杰西卡了
Bobby, stop standing there staring at Jessica.
也让别人有机会欣赏嘛
Give someone else a turn.
我要洗衣服
I'm doing a load.
回你房间去把你脏衣服拿下来
Go up to your room and get your dirties.
我必须得去拿给她了
I--I have to give 'em to her.
不然她会一件件翻我的东西
Otherwise she's gonna go through my stuff,
我有一张我爷爷给我的支票
and I have a check from my grandpa
我可不想被她发现
I don't want her to know about.
克丽斯 我要洗衣服啦
Chrissy! I'm doing a wash!
妈 这次衣服用左右折再对折的折法好吗
And fold everything in threes this time, Ma!
就是要杰西卡以前那种折法
The way Jessica used to!
我再试试 但我又不是完美的神
I'll try, but I'm not perfect.
那是杰西卡的招牌
That was Jessica's thing.
这话没错 妈
Got that right, Ma!
那个女人简直完美无瑕
The woman was without flaws!
这件你可能需要单独洗
You might want to wash that alone.
不管你信不信 它其实是白色的
Believe it or not, it's a white.
麦克斯 你是在干嘛
Max, what are you doing?
别担心 我另一罩还穿着呢
Relax, I have the other one on.
没人会因此受到伤害
No one's gonna get hurt.
我得保持冷静
I just need to stay calm
想出办法来赢取鲍比妈妈欢心
and figure out a way to win Bobby's mother over.
我必须行 我必须行
I have to! I have to!
你在想办法搞到那美滋滋
You trying to get some of that sweet, sweet
爽歪歪的爷爷支票钱吗
grandpa-check money?
他妈的门咋没人去开啊
Somebody get the frickin' door!
我这就去开他妈的门
Uh, I'll get the frickin' door.
别别别别别
No, no, no, no, no.
我得想办法博取他们的好感
I have to win these people over.
他妈的交给我来开 克丽斯
I freaking got it, Chrissy.
棒呆了 绝对帮我"加分"
Oh, great. This should help.
厄尔还有五分钟坐这椅子的时间
Earl's got five more minutes in that chair.
老人我也是说揍就揍
I'll bounce an old man.
轮到谁去检查他还有没有呼吸
Whose turn is it to see if he's breathing?
没死 他还活着
Oh, no, he's okay.
他只是梦到自己在跑步
He's just having a running dream.
你会抓到那只松鼠的 朋友
You'll get that squirrel, buddy.
他没多少椅子时间了
Well, clock's ticking.
瞧 居然没人提这台电视
Look, elephant in the room,
我必须得看看在这电视看黄片是啥感觉
but I got to see what porno looks like on that screen.
就是 瞧
Oh, yeah, look.
我带了《双峰边的曼彻斯特》
I brought "Manchester by the Double D's."
你现在明白我们为什么要学印第安语了吧
You see why we had to learn Navajo?
没关系啦 我妈妈喜欢家里人多
It's all fine. My mother loves having company.
他们不是说笑 而是真的要看啊
Oh, not kidding; they're really going to watch it
塞不进去
It doesn't fit.
这句话感觉我都说了不下千百遍了
Heh, if I had a nickel for every time I've said that.
是啊 他说得没错
Yeah, he's got that right.
鲍比 我告诉过你
Bobby, I told you.
一定要关好前门
You can't leave the front door open.
咱们家离基督教青年会太近了
We live too close to the YMCA.
不 妈妈 这些人是卡洛琳的朋友
No, Ma, these are Caroline's friends.
他们会说印第安语
They speak Navajo.
好吧 希望他们会喜欢意大利菜
Okay, well, I hope they like Italian,
因为老娘费了一晚上功夫做这个
'cause that's what I spent all night making.
我觉得她已经开始慢慢热络起来了
You know, I-- I think she's warming up.
你知道我现在碰到了完美前女友窘境
You see I'm dealing with a perfect ex-girlfriend situation.
我需要你站在我这边帮我
I need you to be on my side.
行啊
Fine.
杰西卡就不会逼人偏袒她 个人意见仅供参考
I don't think Jessica made people take sides, just FYI.
是是是 我想我是时候改变策略
Yeah, I think it's time for me to switch my focus
将攻势从妈妈转移到丹妮斯
from the mom to Denise.
我忘了我其实更擅长跟姐妹们相处
I forgot, I'm actually better with sisters.
我必须行 我必须行
I have to be! I have to be!
你最好能行
Well, you better be.
因为我要跟你说
'Cause I'm gonna tell you the same thing
我对我前男友传教士[式]史提夫也说过的话
I told my old boyfriend, Missionary Steve:
是时候扭转乾坤[换个姿势]了
it's time to turn this thing around.
丹妮斯 你来啦
Denise, there you are!
瞧瞧你 我可喜欢看人白天换行头啦
Oh, look at you. I love a midday costume change.
而你却不准我穿我的吃货长袍来参加派对
And you said I couldn't wear my eating robe to the party.
反正没男人会来
Well, since there aren't gonna be any guys here,
我就早早做好准备上床睡觉啦
I figured I'd just get ready for bed.
哇 那边那个帅哥是谁
Ooh, who's the hottie over there?
是在睡梦中奔跑的那位
The one running in his sleep
还是拿盘子向他腋下搧风的那位
or the one fanning his underarms with a plate?
那个肌肉男
The muscular one.
肌肉男 你得指出来
Muscular? You're gonna have to point.
我们看的是同一个"那边"吗
Is there a different "over there"?
来吧 各位 来餐厅
Come on, guys, in the dining room.
你们一定要尝尝我做的酱汁
You have to taste the sauce I made.
我用的可是杰西卡的秘方哦
I used Jessica's recipe.
超他妈好吃
It's a frickin' delight!
讲话文明点 小妞
Watch your mouth, young lady!
但她说得对
But she's right.
你好呀
Hello.
在我们开始进餐前
Before we start eating,
麦克斯 你来做饭前祷告好吗
Max, would you like to say grace?
感谢...上帝吗
Thanks, God?
还是我来吧
I'll do it.
感谢上帝及祂的母亲
We thank God and his mother,
因为母亲为祂做了一切
'cause we know his mother does everything.
而且祂永远不会未经母亲批准就跟人约会
And he would never date a woman without getting her approval.
好了 妈 我觉得耶稣不太约会的吧
Okay, Ma, I don't think Jesus was a big dater.
至少我认识祂的时候不是
He wasn't when I knew him.
阿憨 我要你跟丹妮斯调情
Han, I need you to flirt with Denise.
-她喜欢你 -我知道啊
- She likes you. - I got that.
她的手正放在我膝盖上
Her hand is on my knee.
啊哦 现在换地方了
Oop, not my knee anymore.
抱歉拿个东西
Excuse my reach.
你喜欢这对宝贝吗 这是我送自己的圣诞礼物
You like them? I got 'em for Christmas.
我们都赞助了
We all chipped in.
杰西卡跟手术的医生是合作关系密切
Jessica worked very closely with the doctor
那医生为她设计了奶头的形状质地
to design the shape texture of the nipples.
我送她一份日历
I got her a calendar.
我虽然不认识这位杰西卡
I don't know who Jessica is,
但我需要这酱汁的食谱
but I need the sauce recipe.
而且我和我可爱的妻子
And my lovely wife and I
不介意一睹那对奶头的芳容
wouldn't mind seeing those nipples at some point.
那对玩意肯定不如这酱汁美味可口
Well, there's no way they're as good as this sauce.
对了 卡洛琳拥有一间甜品酒吧
Anyway, Caroline owns a dessert bar.
那是什么鬼
What the hell is that?
麦克斯 你觉得那酱汁怎么样
Max, what do you think of the sauce?
麦克斯 你"不爱"这味道可以诚实说出来啊
Max, you can be honest if you don't love it.
什么 再来点
What? More.
好啦 我们知道
Okay, we get it.
你喜欢杰西卡的酱汁
You like Jessica's sauce.
我明明已经很饱了
Mmm, you know, I'm so full,
可我还想吃
but I can't stop.
你不一定非要吃啊
You don't have to eat it.
说什么鬼话
Are you crazy?
这可是一生难得吃一次的美味酱汁
This is a once in a lifetime sauce.
我要把我的塑身衣撑到最大
I'm gonna push my Spanx to the limit.
有人愿意跟我换一下座位吗
Could someone switch seats with me?
怎么回事 丹妮斯
What's going on over there, Denise?
你是不是又对别人毛手毛脚了
You keeping your hands to yourself?
那我坐她旁边好了
Uh, I'll sit next to her.
我想过去坐在卡洛琳旁边
I'd like to move down and sit next to Caroline.
所以现在你不想坐在你妈旁边了吗
Oh, so now you don't want to sit next to your mother?
反正我也不饿
I'm not hungry anyway.
我要上楼洗澡了
I'm gonna go upstairs and take a shower.
我们家的浴帘有一个大洞哦
There's a big hole in our shower curtain.
谢谢邀请 但我只用一款医生处方的肥皂
Thanks, but I use a doctor-prescribed soap.
多谢"帮忙"啊 阿憨
Thanks a lot, Han.
你就不能为了我去跟她洗个鸳鸯浴吗
You couldn't just take a shower with her for me?
妈 我的那份呢
Ma! Where's my plate?
谁能帮忙拿份面上去给克丽斯
Could somebody take a plate up to Chrissy?
她还是很伤心不愿意出房门
She's still too upset to come out.
-你们也知道是因为... -我们知道 妈
- You know, because of-- - We know, Ma.
我去吧
I'll do it.
因为我压根不喜欢这酱汁
'Cause I--I don't even like this sauce.
不 我给克丽斯送上去好了
No, I'll--I'll bring Chrissy her plate.
她是我最后的机会
She's my last chance.
帮我留点那个酱汁
And save me some of that sauce.
那是我吃过最好吃的东西
It's the best thing I've ever had.
别担心 我会帮你装满你的包包
Don't worry, I filled your purse with it.
没有人干活的吗
Does anyone work here?
我的食物呢
Where's my food?
哎哟哟 杰西卡
Well, well, well, Jessica.
你或许会做很棒的酱汁
You may make a great sauce,
但你阻止不了我
but you can't stop me.
发生什么事了
What's going on out there?
我听到有东西打碎了
I heard a crash!
啥事都没有
Uh, everything's fine!
外面有辆卡车撞了个小孩
A truck hit a kid outside.
麦克斯 你能过来一下吗
Max, can you come here for a second?
刚才那阵骚动是什么
What's all the commotion?
如果没食物 让我怎么消化我的情绪啊
I can't eat my frickin' feelings if there's no food!
撞的是骑自行车的小孩吗
Was the kid on a bike?
天啊 你对杰西卡做了什么
Oh, my God! Look what you did to Jessica!
你为什么这么嫉妒她 卡洛琳
Why are you so jealous of her, Caroline?
你永远也当不了杰西卡好吗 我们谁都不行
You'll never be Jessica, okay? None of us will!
不是我干的
I didn't do it!
她自己从墙上掉下来
She just fell off the wall.
麦克斯 她想害死我
Max, she is trying to destroy me.
老娘的食物呢
Where's my food?
我又要开始狂挠胳膊了啊
I'm starting to scratch my arms again!
好吧 我来搞定照片
Okay, I'll fix the picture.
把我这盘给她吧
Give her my plate.
等等
Hang on.
让我再多吃一大口
Let me just take one more big bite.
也让我吃点
Give me a little of that.
去你妈的 杰西卡
Oh, damn you, Jessica!
麦克斯 你是怎么弄好杰西卡的照片的
Max, how did you fix Jessica's picture?
看起来简直完美
It looks perfect!
不太容易
Wasn't easy.
我尽量避免跟她有眼神接触
I tried not to make eye contact with her,
因为我开始对她有感情了
'cause I was starting to get feelings.
你在这儿啊
Hey, there you are.
你还好吗 我知道我的家人很难相处
Are you okay? I know my family can be a lot.
没有啦 我待得很开心
No, I'm having a great time.
你觉得你妈需要人帮忙把马卡龙拿出来吗
You think your mom needs help putting out that macaron?
我注意到她还没拆包装
I noticed they're not out.
我还注意到有一个在鸟笼里
I also noticed one in the birdcage.
如果你待得不开心
You know what? If you're not having a good time,
我们随时可以走
we can leave.
我是一个成年人 不用总听妈妈的话
I'm a grown man. She's not the boss of me.
-鲍比 -马上来 妈
- Bobby! - Coming, Ma!
卡洛琳 放轻松
Caroline, relax.
没人会立刻喜欢上你
Nobody likes you right away.
我是一直到去年才喜欢上
I just got there last year,
而且直到现在感情还很多雷区
and there's still a lot of red flags.
谢谢你借我穿丹妮斯的毛毯袍
Thank you for letting me borrow Denise's Snuggie.
感觉我又回到我妈子宫里了呢
I feel like I'm back in the womb again.
不过这"子宫"里没有满是烟味
But it doesn't reek of cigarettes.
等等
Wait.
好像有烟味
I think it does.
我喜欢
I like it.
今晚这件衣服脱在地上时 我会更喜欢
I'm gonna like it even more when it's on the floor tonight.
那人还有气儿吗
Is that one still breathing?
好啦 妈 我要去练空手道啦
All right, Ma, I'm going to karate.
空手道吗
Karate?
哎哟哟
Well, well, well.
跆拳道向你问好
Tae Kwon Hello.
我还是个黄带[基础]呢
I happen to be a yellow belt.
是吗
Oh, yeah?
是的
Oh, yeah.
我从鸟笼里拿出了五个马卡龙
I got five of the macaron back from the birdcage.
我明天把毛毯袍还给你
I'll get your Snuggie back to you by tomorrow.
明早鲍比从卡洛琳家走
I'll give to Bobby in the morning
我就顺便把袍子给他
when he leaves Caroline's.
你不是说你在布莱恩家睡吗
You said you slept at Brian's.
你现在开始骗我了吗
You lying to me now?
妈
Ma...
我昨晚在卡洛琳家过夜
I was with Caroline last night.
但我没看到他的裸体
But I didn't see him naked.
我看到了 我们浴室的门不能锁
I did. Our bathroom door doesn't lock.
我看出他为啥是你最爱的孩子了 太太
I see why he's your favorite, Mrs. F.
我们在看东西
Uh, we're watching something.
你们能不能去其他地方说话
Can you two talk somewhere else?
没关系啦 我开大声点
It's fine. I'll turn it up.
遥 遥控器在哪里
Where--where's the remote?
妈 我会订了要跟人家订婚
Whoa, Ma, I--I only got engaged to be engaged
纯粹是因为爸爸生病 我希望你开心点
'cause Dad was sick, and I wanted you to be happy.
可现在我跟卡洛琳在一起了
But now I'm with Caroline, and...
而她让我很快乐
Caroline makes me happy.
-我有吗 -她有吗
- I do? - She does?
有啊
You do.
她有的
She does.
-好啦 是... -是上天的旨意
- Okay, it was-- - Uh, it was a sign...
或许杰西卡不应该再被挂在那里了
that Jessica didn't belong there anymore.
其实呢 你给我的鲍比带来笑容
You know what? You make my Bobby smile.
而他笑的时候比平常更帅了
And he's even more handsome when he smiles.
克丽斯 下楼来见卡洛琳
Chrissy, come down and meet Caroline!
她正点吗 我最讨厌丑逼了 妈
She hot? Cause I don't like uggos, Ma.
她美呆了
She's gorgeous.
她长得像我
She looks like me.
除了比我多了点胡子
Just with a little more mustache.
欢迎来到我们家 姑娘们
Welcome to our home, girls.
-谢谢 -谢谢
- Oh, thank you! - Thank you!
你都不知道这对我有多大意义
You have no idea how much this means to me!
你试试挣脱我这固定术
Try and get out of this hold.
谁告诉你我想挣脱了
Who says I want to?
下周日同一时间见吗
So same time next Sunday?